<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>8amiul&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 8amiul&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 19:49:38 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Termus</title>
      <link>/project/termus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/termus/</guid>
      <description>https://github.com/8amiul/termus Video Demo: https://youtu.be/GzHTSfeRQZU Description: Termus is a terminal based music player written in C using SDL_mixer and ncurses library.
Files: main.c : initialize libraries and functions are called termus.c: Manage keystrokes, free up memory and helping functions file.c : Manages directories, scan music and prepares music files for playing video.c : Functions regarding displaying windows and playing music termes.h: A header file containing functon declaration and structs Used Libraries SDL2 &amp;amp; SDL2_mixer: SDL2_mixer is used for audio and music management ncurses: For displaying windows and text Functions termus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thedailystar-CLI</title>
      <link>/project/thedailystar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/thedailystar/</guid>
      <description>https://github.com/8amiul/Thedailystar-CLI Video Demo: https://youtu.be/5Tp4xeqNLEc Description Thedailystar-CLI is a terminal based program written in python for CS50&amp;rsquo;s Introduction to Programming with Python. This program does scrape news from The Daily Star
Files project.py: The main program. test_project.py: To test project.py using pytest. Used Libraries BeautifulSoup4: For scraping data from The Daily Star. curses: For handling keyboard input and user interface. requests: For sending HTTP requests. pytest: For testing functions built in program About Functions def menu(stdscr, test_= None): This function shows the start menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First meal of 2025</title>
      <link>/posts/first_meal_2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 19:49:38 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/first_meal_2025/</guid>
      <description>I just cooked my first meal of this year. So it&amp;rsquo;s a new year and Today I woke up early.
I just thought it&amp;rsquo;s better I try something new today. So why don&amp;rsquo;t I make my own breakfast?
Noodles was the only food I knew how to cook. So I started cooking. I took noodles, then egg and some veggies (actually left over salad from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s party).
However it wasn&amp;rsquo;t cooked properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodlock</title>
      <link>/posts/goodlock/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 14:14:53 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/goodlock/</guid>
      <description>My phone has One Ui 4.1 core. Which is crap! None of the GoodLock modules are supported on my phone. But with some tweaking we can achieve this feature. But the phone has to be rooted.
Our First aim is to download the patched version of GoodLock.
Then we have to disable the apk signature verification check. Why do we need that? Just because those apk doesn&amp;rsquo;t come with any signature.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
