<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>website on 8amiul&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>https://8amiul.github.io/tags/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in website on 8amiul&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:04:04 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://8amiul.github.io/tags/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Github Pages Appear on Google</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/make-your-github-pages-appear-on-google/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:04:04 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/make-your-github-pages-appear-on-google/</guid>
      <description>
    &lt;style&gt;
    .post-content img, .post-content a img{
        align-self: center;
        max-width: 100%; 
        width: 1000px; 
        height: auto; 
        padding: 0.5rem 1rem 0.5rem 1rem;
    }
    &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making github pages appear on google search is pretty easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have to use Google Search Console for that. It will not only make your site indexed but also it gives you many site monitoring features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://search.google.com/search-console/welcome&#34;&gt;Google Search Console&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to login with your Google account or if logged in already then switch your Google account to your desired one.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/github-pages-on-google/google-search-console.png&#34; alt=&#34;[google-search-console-screenshot]&#34; title=&#34;Google Search Console&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a section called URL prefix. You have to input your website address there (ex: &lt;a href=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io&#34;&gt;https://8amiul.github.io&lt;/a&gt;). Clicking continue will make a page appear looking like this.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/github-pages-on-google/google-search-console-2.png&#34; alt=&#34;[google-search-console-screenshot]&#34; title=&#34;Google Search Console&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many sub sections such as HTML file, HTML tag and many other. But I personally have chosen the HTML tag method. It is the easiest one I&amp;rsquo;ll say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Expanding that HTML tag section will reveal a HTML code that you have to put in your site. Copy it or keep it somewhere cause we will need it later. Hit done and that page should be gone but you can access that page again buy opening the &lt;code&gt;Search property&lt;/code&gt; tab, your site should be mentioned there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now it&amp;rsquo;s time we pasted the code that have copied before in to the header file. As I am using hugo to build this side. My site structure might not be the same for you. Basically the baseof.html which resides at &lt;code&gt;layouts/_default/&lt;/code&gt; is responsible of giving the site structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the copied tag a meta tag that means we have to put it inside the head element in our website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My website&amp;rsquo;s pages are divided in separate files. I&amp;rsquo;ve files for header (navbar), head, footer etc. So all the code for head element is inside the head.html which resides at &lt;code&gt;layouts/partials/head.html&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In simple terms, just make sure this code is presented on all the pages of your site. That will do.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/github-pages-on-google/google-search-console-3.png&#34; alt=&#34;[head.html]&#34; title=&#34;head.html&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just paste the copied code inside the head tag and try not to keep it at the bottom of the head tag. Now just publish your site on GitHub. After maybe a few days you have to visit the Google Search Console and hit verify. If you&amp;rsquo;ve done everything properly then you may see the green light of success.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img style=&#34;width: 500px;&#34; src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/github-pages-on-google/verify_success.png&#34; alt=&#34;[head.html]&#34; title=&#34;head.html&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you should be able to see your site on Google. If you still don&amp;rsquo;t find then wait a few more days, it should appear.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript is fun</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/javascript-is-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 22:43:24 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/javascript-is-fun/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big fan of JavaScript. But later I realized that JS is so necessary for front-end web development. I recently just implemented an image viewer kind of page in my website, which needed JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually don&amp;rsquo;t know about JavaScript yet. There is a part of JavaScript
that connects it&amp;rsquo;s functionality with HTML and CSS, that is called Document Object Model aka DOM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The syntax is a bit like C. As I am comfortable with C so JavaScript is also not really giving me much pain. But it is way more bigger than C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The basic concept of programming languages are the same. You&amp;rsquo;ll have variable, loops, arrays, different kind of data types, functions, libraries to make life easier, OOP (maybe) and&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s all ig. So I am just learning the syntax and as well as some new features that come across while implementing more things in my site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would like to mention few resources which I found helpful,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://javascript.info/&#34;&gt;javascript.info&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/JavaScript&#34;&gt;MDN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/5fb2aPlgoys&#34;&gt;A YouTube video for DOM&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally, &lt;a href=&#34;https://chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;ChatGPT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think learning by making a project does work better than following a tutorial.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rss feed!</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/rss/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:24:58 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/rss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;rss feed is like a magazine where you can link many favourite webpages which provides a rss.xml thing. So with that you can view all the main contents of those websites without visiting every site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t know about rss feeds before building this site. I knew that icon on blog pages but never understood what actually rss was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now my site also got a rss feed. Hugo, yes that&amp;rsquo;s what I used to generate this static site of mine. So hugo auto generates a rss.xml file that contains everything we need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there was a problem at first. By default it wasn&amp;rsquo;t set up properly. On the rss reader my site wasn&amp;rsquo;t rendered correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just to fix this I had to implement a code in hugo&amp;rsquo;s mytheme/layouts/_default/rss.xml. Well, I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to understand that code.
It works for me, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t get executed in my system and once again it works for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gideonwolfe.com/posts/sysadmin/hugo/hugorss/&#34;&gt;Code can be found here!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/spacecowboy/Feeder&#34;&gt;feeder&lt;/a&gt; on my phone and on linux I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/newsboat/newsboat&#34;&gt;newsboat&lt;/a&gt; to view rss feeds.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>