<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>daily-things on 8amiul&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>https://8amiul.github.io/tags/daily-things/</link>
    <description>Recent content in daily-things on 8amiul&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:13:55 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://8amiul.github.io/tags/daily-things/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Recent Exams</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/aug-25/thoughts-on-recent-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:13:55 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/aug-25/thoughts-on-recent-exams/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently made a post about my sufferings due to biology exam. Surprisingly it went nice. Perhaps I wasn&amp;rsquo;t the person who deserved such smooth exam. I was quite unsure of that exam as I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the will to study. All praise to the almighty!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides everything, I was confident with my math exam. Because I thought I like to solve problems. I can stick with a problem until I solve it, I have that patience. But sadly this type of thing doesn&amp;rsquo;t get that much value here in this type of exams or in any exams. Exam is not only about solving problems by thinking critically. Here one has a limited time and within that time one must answer those. Otherwise you be dead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I realized that I could solve problems but just only when I am in my room lying in my bed. If you live in Bangladesh and keep knowledge about the students. Then you might already heard that, this year questions are a bit weird. By saying weird I mean that something we didn&amp;rsquo;t expected. Everyone thought that like every year boards will follow the trend. But it didn&amp;rsquo;t happened so nicely this year. They chose randomness and they did it right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will not blame the board for making such questions. If I do, then I clearly trying to blame others for my inability. I am not trying to be so different than others by stating such fact. I don&amp;rsquo;t even care wether they make questions difficult or easy as I don&amp;rsquo;t really count this exam so fancy thing in my life. Society might consider it as a valuable exam but does this exam even justify anything of a student?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t justify the full potential of a human or a student. It might give you a preliminary idea about a person. Sometimes that idea even goes wrong. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen countless people those who didn&amp;rsquo;t do well in HSC but still they are living a good life. They are brilliant and they are no lesser than any other talented students. Now let us get back to the topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, questions were so freaking difficult. Not everyone could answer it properly. Those who are talented students, they could only answer those. Then would get A+. However, in this way, we can exclude people those who doesn&amp;rsquo;t deserve an A+. Thus, we can normalize the fact that getting 4.69 isn&amp;rsquo;t a bad result. Consider only 60 people got A+ in Dhaka board. Then will our parents and the society gonna compare all of us with those 60 people? If they do then it will be pathetic. I believe they will not do. But if 70% students get A+ and the rest can not, then definitely there will be people to say why you weren&amp;rsquo;t in that 70%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From my POV and with my ignorance, I&amp;rsquo;ll say that questions were easy for those who studied. I didn&amp;rsquo;t study so I must not find it easy. If I had studied I would have found it easier. This is the fact here. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to blame the other for my failure. Today it was the worst HSC exam I have ever attended! But still I have that strength to subdue the sadness that occurs or the tendency of blaming others for my own failure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday to me!</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/july-25/happy-birthday-to-myself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:41:46 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/july-25/happy-birthday-to-myself/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally, I am 20! Not really excited but glad to come this far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never really celebrated my birthday in a grand manner. The last time I cut a cake, I was probably 10 years old. Yeah, 15 years ago. I never really felt like cutting cakes, blowing candles, getting gifts or anything else. All I wanted was just to be with my friends and family. As a kid I learned that people cut cakes on their birthday. I remembered I also did and I was happy too. Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t like cakes, gifts and etc things? Once we had a party at our house. Maybe some of my cousins and friends were there. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember how old I was. I must have been happy then.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now birthdays are just a day where I know that in this day I was born. Still special dishes are made, my parents and sibling do wish me at 12 O&amp;rsquo;clock just to make me happy. Just to show that they care about me and want to make me happy. When they wished me today, it felt so nice. I just thanked them. What more I could do. At least I&amp;rsquo;ve got some people who care for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year, I don&amp;rsquo;t remember what I did on my birthday. It was chaos everywhere in our country. Lived an isolated time and without internet. But one thing I still remember, a birthday wish, made my day even in the worst time of that year. This year, that wish is nowhere to be found. If I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so excited about that then maybe today I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t sound so low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I appreciate those people who wished me today. You, just a few people, have made my day. I don&amp;rsquo;t know how you got my birthday in your mind. That doesn&amp;rsquo;t even matter. What matters is that you have remembered me and wished me today. I hope you get to fullfil your dreams and live a healthy and happy life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, bit of a gloomy birthday I am having. I could be happy if I were not brining unwanted thoughts out of nowhere. I guess a sleep will get rid of those things that I am afraid of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah, one thing, my posts are now filled with non-tech shit. I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting some actual stuff rather than spreading bullshit. FUCK THE REMINISCENCE!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I hate studying biology</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/july-25/i-hate-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:41:48 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/july-25/i-hate-biology/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Another note is gonna, probably, make me fall asleep. Whenever I try to write something, I start feeling asleep. Thus, I say to myself that the topic can go to hell and why should I talk about it and I sleep. Hopefully, I will not be writing this note fully like all the other unpublished notes. Tonight, I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything specific to talk about. It will be about what I am going through right now. Within a day, I will be attending the Biology exam. I never liked Biology and never wanted to learn because it is a pain to study biology in our curriculum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Biology is a nice subject I will say. It&amp;rsquo;s interesting when I study it willingly . But when the curriculum forces me to  memorize the reactions of photosynthesis and respiration, gymnosperms and angiosperms, all those diversities of species and every possible bullshit, It is unbearable. I am reluctant to study biology. I took it as an optional subject. Though, it is optional but it is rather more important than any other subjects cause it can increase points on those subjects where I may not get A+.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a tendency to not do something that I don&amp;rsquo;t like. Manly which needs a lot of memorization. Math is also about memorization. Some say it isn&amp;rsquo;t but at one point it is. All those formulas and types where we can&amp;rsquo;t go further if we are unaware about any of these. But still math is enjoyable. Formulas can easily be memorized by writing it a few times. Even organic chemistry seems easier than biology. Sounds funny, right? But it&amp;rsquo;s my perspective. I ain&amp;rsquo;t a good student who&amp;rsquo;s getting A+ this time but still it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make me inept at determining the difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, hope this phase of Biology goes quick and obviously well. Later I&amp;rsquo;ll have math to deal with. It won&amp;rsquo;t be so exhausting like biology. I am not saying I am good with math but at least I have an interest in studying it. I am waiting till this thing ends. I would be happy if they didn&amp;rsquo;t allot that much gap between exams. It sucks my energy badly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what I&amp;rsquo;ll be doing tomorrow. Problem, just going to accept the fate. Now just before the exam, now I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything in mind. Pretty, tough situation. I wish there was nothing called society. If the society wasn&amp;rsquo;t there to judge me by my results then probably students wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be so terrified of getting poor marks. At least I can say that they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t hang themselves. Not a big fan of suicide. Our society has to change their mindset. Maybe it will happen one day but it will take so many years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another &lt;a href=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/posts/may-25/awful-day/&#34;&gt;Awful day&lt;/a&gt; incarcerated!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacrifice</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/jun-25/eid-al-adha-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/jun-25/eid-al-adha-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Can&amp;rsquo;t really start with some joyful words this time. But it&amp;rsquo;s eid and eid mubarak! Eid is indeed not eiding!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This eid is pretty messed up. Last time on Eid al-fitr it was better than my expectations. As I said, every family reunion is the best moment of my life. It actually happened last time. It&amp;rsquo;s just not about the eid but we had a wedding ceremony for my cousin just a few weeks before. So due to that the eid also became a bit more exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qurbani eid, as we mainly say so I better continue with this. Last year I was so active on these, such as visiting the cattle market with friends. This year I didn&amp;rsquo;t even get the smell of the cattle market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This eid doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like an eid because I&amp;rsquo;ve got a damn exam coming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s eid and like always I&amp;rsquo;ll say to celebrate it with friends and family. Be happy and make the surroundings happy. This eid is special. We gotta sac and make some partitions, one for you, one for them and one for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, let us sac the animal outside and sac the evil inside and Eid Mubarak!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awful Day</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/may-25/awful-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:40:18 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/may-25/awful-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Not the best day it was. The last post was about a wonderful day. I was fine that day. But this day I ain&amp;rsquo;t doing well. There is a saying, &amp;ldquo;A healthy mind in a healthy body.&amp;rdquo; My body and mind aren&amp;rsquo;t so close to fine. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t really make good use of time today. That upcoming exam&amp;hellip; is just a &amp;ldquo;let it happen&amp;rdquo; thing now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This pain in my body got me nicely. I&amp;rsquo;ve been facing it for the last two days. This type of pain neither lets me sit nor lie in bed. As the pain has become unbearable, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help visiting the doc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doc didn&amp;rsquo;t do much. Just prescribed me some meds and, obviously, some freaking tests. Doing these tests is so time-consuming and a great hassle. I had to complete 6 medical tests. And it took five hours! It wouldn&amp;rsquo;t take time if these tests didn&amp;rsquo;t have many requirements. Also, a long queue I had to go through, so definitely it would take that much time. Wasting much time just before my board exam! Unfortunate circumstances are surely unavoidable. Sometimes people curse doctors just because they prescribe so many tests. I am also annoyed. But we can&amp;rsquo;t deny the fact that these tests are for us and just to determine the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How much does it take to be a professional doctor? It takes years and a lot of dedication to get those acronyms beside one&amp;rsquo;s name. Can AI replace all the doctors?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever, I always forget to take earphones with me before going somewhere. I regret it a lot! I can waste a lot of time scrolling social media at home, but whenever I go somewhere, I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel like scrolling much. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel so joyful for some reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On these devastating days I miss some people. I wish they were here. At least I could share what I am feeling, as I used to share everything with them. It actually feels good if I have my family, friends, and loved ones stay by my side. I once didn&amp;rsquo;t feel so alone. Sadly, doing certain activities still makes me upset and makes me miss them. It&amp;rsquo;s not actually&amp;hellip; but I miss that I&amp;hellip; I don&amp;rsquo;t know. Though, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually make me upset, but rather it makes me tranquil. I just wonder. I don&amp;rsquo;t even wonder. No, I wonder about those days. Nature somehow reminds me of those.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to forget all the things; maybe some I wanna forget. I believe we may not have been the best with each other, but that time taught me and made me feel a lot of things. I learned how it feels to be with them. People come, people go, but their taught lessons and memories remain. Insensible somewhere deep inside us which sometimes gets its sense, such as mine got in sense today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I thought them got me and me got them but them got people and me got none. That makes me laugh sometimes. Them will get people and me will keep misleading myself by thinking them are for me and me are for them. Yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;them&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo; manner; it sounds cool to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So they were fine, are fine, will be fine, and I&amp;hellip; also am good. They keep telling me to just get over it. Then I asked myself, &amp;ldquo;Did we start to just get over it?&amp;rdquo; I still don&amp;rsquo;t know the answer. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t the most honest person. Pretty much I was not the best guy that someone should deserve. Yet, a lot to improve. They taught me that, and I found it legit. I tried everything. But I had my own issues. Pretty bad issues, I guess. I sometimes ask myself, &amp;ldquo;Wasn&amp;rsquo;t I the best for them?&amp;rdquo; Then I asked myself, &amp;ldquo;Didn&amp;rsquo;t you suck their blood?&amp;rdquo; I answered in the affirmative. They said I sucked their blood and got on their nerves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I just ask myself why they had even chosen me! Look at this ugly-ass shit with a disgusting demeanor and a freaking scrub. Ayoo, I am just exaggerating about myself, nothing else. I don&amp;rsquo;t often represnt myself in this way. But sometimes exaggerating is okay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What we think, we become.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, just exaggerated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, it must have been an unfortunate choice for them. Probably a situation where they can&amp;rsquo;t decide whether to stay or to leave. I appreciate the good memories they offered and the lessons they taught. I hope they do well in life. It feels good to see people doing well who got potential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a few days they got their birthday. This year I don&amp;rsquo;t even stand a chance to wish or say some shit. For them it should be their new people to enjoy with… maybe. What to do! It&amp;rsquo;s up to them, right? Who am I to say? Nobody.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I miss them, it&amp;rsquo;s true, and who doesn&amp;rsquo;t want companies when BSOD is popping in their life? I wish I could get back to that point in life and resolve all the conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes life is good, and sometimes it becomes a bit harsh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s not talk anymore about this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was about an awful day. You see, we can talk a lot about the awful things that have happened to us, but we can&amp;rsquo;t really describe what wonderful things have happened to us or what one has done to us that briefly. For example, my last post. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t so brief or with overwhelmed emotions like this one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess that was it. If you are facing pain in your body, then take some freaking NSAIDs and pay the fees of the doc. Got nobody to talk to? Write some words on the rock or wood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It helps and actually saves you from many inconveniences too. Peace!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonderful Day</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/may-25/wonderful-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:37:49 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/may-25/wonderful-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is a wonderful day for me. It’s raining and rain reminds me of my childhood. I still remember that I used to play video games on my uncle’s computer on rainy days. It’s not like I missed school because of rain. My luck wasn’t so great that time. I would pray for a rain fall so that I could skip school but sadly It had always rained when I was about to return home. If you are from Dhaka then you may know that sometimes Dhaka becomes that nice city from Italy called Venice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now we don’t see that Venice here cause it has been fixed and we city dwellers are greatful. At least I don’t see Venice here where I live but still there are many places where you can see it to happen. Also too much rain fall can cause this and which happened few months ago. Let’s not discuss this topic anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, I would return from school and get fresh then I would obviously turn on the computer to play games on it. I only had a single game that I liked most which was Grand Theft Auto Vice City. On that time it was the most popular games among kids. Cause you could do anything there kill innocent people, smash cars, blow up anything with panzer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have ever played the modified GTA VC then you might be familiar with its radio. It was filled with Bangla and Hindi songs. I liked to listen to “Shada” and it was from Minar, a talented artist. It’s nostalgic song.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always liked rain fall cause it gives nature its true face. I used to go with my friends to play football on these days. My parents said that I would fall sick because of it. But who cares about being sick when we got people with us! I actually used to get sick though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a thing that I hate on these days. Which is it makes me feel like that everything is so dampy or wet. That sort of feeling would freak me out. I feel everything is so messed up. Kind of like it used to trigger OCD that time, even though I don’t have it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sleeping on those rainy days was something I always wanted. What more one can desire? I desire of delicious meals, a cozy bed and a device where I can listen music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t feel like writing anymore. Let us do chill on a rainy days!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did I have a cold drink that day?</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/may-25/cold-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 14:27:39 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/may-25/cold-drink/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I actually don&amp;rsquo;t remember. It was a year ago. I just got into college. Traveling was so tiring for me and, I believe, for everyone living in Dhaka. That enormous traffic and pollution was enough to put myself down. I was new to college, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t know the best route to reach there. I used to travel by bus. Which wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best way of traveling. But at least the way it was, which I knew at that time. Then days passed, and I found another path, which has its own pros and cons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So about cold drinks, I used to become so thirsty as I had to walk a lot. I would crave something cold. I mostly wanted a nice lemonade. I could have a simple one from a roadside vendor, but it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be so tasteful. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s a matter of hygiene. But it&amp;rsquo;s not like I haven&amp;rsquo;t had lemonade from them. I had quite a lot. I used to go to college with one of my friends. We had to walk a lot; we sometimes stopped to get a lemonade. It actually attracts us to go there. Humidity and tiredness would make us want something cold. Also, it looks so nice to see lemons, ice cubes, and people drinking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was actually tasty. I saw how they make it. It&amp;rsquo;s so simple and fast. What they do is just add a little lemon, obviously water, and ice cubes. Nobody knows about its origin. Those ice cubes can even be from the morgue; who cares? All I want is temporary satisfaction. So ice cubes and an unknown recipe looked like salt. Some kind of mixture it was. Then mix it and serve. Quite easy!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drinking that would satisfy me, but it would make me a bit more exhausted. I don&amp;rsquo;t know why. I know it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be the case, but it happens to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Damn, that was a long road and quite a hassle. Getting on a bus and having a seat was an amazing challenge at that time. I have made a lot of bad choices in my life. One of them was choosing a college that was 9 km far from my home. It might not be a huge distance for people around the world. But here it is a great distance. Time is a valuable thing. Taking decisions like this costs both energy and time. So it means it was just nothing but ruining a beautiful day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, I have passed those days. I don&amp;rsquo;t have to go to college anymore. I have a bigger challenge. Maybe when I&amp;rsquo;m in university I&amp;rsquo;ll have to go through this kind of hassle once again. That&amp;rsquo;s how it works here, right? Or maybe everywhere. Suffering is everywhere; suffering is for everyone. One suffers through poverty and another through abundance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So how was life back then? I thought I had enough time for everything. I didn&amp;rsquo;t know or never tried to understand that time flies so fast. I had a lot of dreams to fulfill. A different ambition, different mindset, different companionship, and different future assumptions. Now I am standing at this date, and I see everything so differently. It didn&amp;rsquo;t go according to my assumptions or plans. It&amp;rsquo;s not the worst, though, but a lot of things have changed, and I am trying my best to get adjusted to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a huge post I&amp;rsquo;ve written that goes with my life. Not a very great life-changing speech it is. But why must we always seek motivation?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, let me mention some of the realizations that I&amp;rsquo;ve made and end this shit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accept unexpected consequences and changes in life because it&amp;rsquo;s an uncertain simulation of the creator of this world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone&amp;rsquo;s replacement is on the way, and when the replacement arrives, one may replace it with no remorse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s flower may become tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s thorn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taking a nap and drinking enough water can sometimes be a solution to a problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Major decisions should be taken in daylight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take less stress and be optimistic, because life is what you make it. It is painful if you see one better than you, and it is joyous if the better one is you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, people will try to suck your blood, but you gotta point them toward somewhere else of you so they can suck that instead. (ifykyk)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t have anything to post, so I did post my thoughts here. It might not help you, but it helps me. We have nothing in our control. We neither can control us nor them. What we have in control is our judgment. How do we accept and how do we not.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End of Ramadan</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/march-25/eid_al-fitr-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 12:46:13 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/march-25/eid_al-fitr-25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;eid-mubarak&#34;&gt;Eid Mubarak!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Ramadan wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best or productive one. However, celebrating eid shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be denied. Hopefully we&amp;rsquo;ll have a peaceful and a happy eid this year. We should visit our family, friends, neighbors and celebrate with everyone. Let us be part of ones celebration and let them be part of ours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How fast time flies! 2023, 24 and now 25. I had another blog post about eid that was published in 2023. I wrote a lot of things about eid on that post. Later I understood that not everyone can celebrate eid. You obviously need family, friends and the mental peace. So, a lot to consider. Yes, it has been two years and a lot has changed!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>90s anime</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/march-25/90s-anime/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 20:26:44 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/march-25/90s-anime/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a big fan of anime. At this date, people are quite familiar with these japanese culture. In order to understand them I thought of adopting some changes. So I started watching anime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am someone who is pretty obsessed with old retro stuff. So there were chances that I might like anime those were made back in 80/90s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have watched some retro anime then you must have noticed the variation of art styles. Those anime seems more vibrant to me. I feel like the actual japanese culture does reflect on those.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;serial-experiments-lain&#34;&gt;Serial Experiments Lain&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I at first started with &amp;lsquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://myanimelist.net/anime/339/Serial_Experiments_Lain&#34;&gt;Serial Experiments Lain&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/march-25/90s-anime/lain1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;[lain]&#34; title=&#34;lain&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/march-25/90s-anime/lain2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;[lain]&#34; title=&#34;lain&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“If you’re not remembered, then you never existed.” – Lain Iwakura&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was kind of&amp;hellip; about a girl who knew nothing about computers turned into a geek and then there lot of things happened which I should not mention. Just watch it if you haven&amp;rsquo;t yet. It got 8 of 10 on &lt;em&gt;myanimelist.net&lt;/em&gt; and I guess it deserves that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now it&amp;rsquo;s time I mention some tragic anime which is a bit devastating to watch. However, I liked every aspect of these two anime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;grave-of-the-fireflies&#34;&gt;Grave of the Fireflies&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or &lt;em&gt;Hotaru no Haka&lt;/em&gt; is a perfect example of what I like.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/march-25/90s-anime/grave1.jpg&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/march-25/90s-anime/grave2.jpg&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/march-25/90s-anime/grave3.jpg&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It highlighted everything about war. How the people suffers, what starvation makes one to do, losing closest ones, hardships of orphans and homeless. Also, you can take life lessons from this one. You&amp;rsquo;ll see that clearly in that anime. In this world, every activity holds something valuable which is worth learning. So i&amp;rsquo;ts obvious that one can learn something by watching anime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This kind of war movies shows that how innocent people suffers and give their life just because of the pride of the empire and rulers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever, the next one is so badly underrated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;barefoot-gen&#34;&gt;Barefoot Gen&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;or &lt;em&gt;Hadashi no Gen&lt;/em&gt; is so underrated and I don&amp;rsquo;t know why it wasn&amp;rsquo;t rated at least 8 out of 10. It&amp;rsquo;s also a historical movie about the atomic bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/march-25/90s-anime/gen2.jpg&#34;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/march-25/90s-anime/gen1.jpg&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has plenty of tragic scenes which I liked. Kind of same as the previous anime as both of them have a common theme. Here you can find the hardship of people. Lack of food, fighting for food, frequent air raid and bombing, shelters, effects of an atomic bomb etc etc. There are also some creative dialogues and scenes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just mention one here,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gen: Shinji, what did you say to make Mother cry like that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shinji: Gee, all I did was ask if I could suck on the fish bones when she was done with them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gen: You&amp;rsquo;re kidding, you asked her that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shinji: Yeah, that was it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gen: [hits Shinji on the head] Idiot!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am obsessed with this kind of anime. I would like to watch more of these and I am searching for underrated 90s anime. If you have something for me then let me know I would be grateful to you. Yes, so this was me enjoying anime.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Dream</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/march-25/lucid-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:47:30 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/march-25/lucid-dream/</guid>
      <description>
    &lt;style&gt;
    .post-content img, .post-content a img{
        align-self: center;
        max-width: 100%; 
        width: 1000px; 
        height: auto; 
        padding: 0.5rem 1rem 0.5rem 1rem;
    }
    &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dream is a fascinating phenomena. There are few types of dream. Some has an aspiration, that&amp;rsquo;s one kind of dream, some see they are being haunted by a huge human like entity who got no facial structure just like a mannequin, some see many other interesting things&amp;hellip; which is not our matter of discussion. However, Lucid dreaming is something which allows us to control what we see in our dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, It&amp;rsquo;s kind of like the scene from Mr. Robot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mind Awake, body asleep&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/lucid-dream/mr-robot.webp&#34; alt=&#34;[mr-robot]&#34; title=&#34;Mr. Robot&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, you&amp;rsquo;ll have the full access to do everything, have the allowance to choose and face consequences. But achieving a lucid dream isn&amp;rsquo;t a piece of cake. I was able to lucid dream after continuously trying for a week. You may fail at first attempt, but one can do anything if he has the will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I should share some tips which are followed by lucid dreamers in order to get this insane thing,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought why do we see dreams so vividly when it&amp;rsquo;s early in the morning? around 4-5 o&amp;rsquo;clock. That&amp;rsquo;s the best time for you to lucid dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now get ready to sacrifice your sleep and mental health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wbtb---wake-back-to-bed&#34;&gt;WBTB - Wake Back To Bed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set an alarm for 30 minutes or an hour after you fall asleep. Try to wake up multiple times like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you&amp;rsquo;ll wake up try staying for at least 5 minutes. On those 5 minutes try to write down what you&amp;rsquo;ve seen, what you&amp;rsquo;ll see or just think that you have to lucid dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was the first technique called WBTB-Wake Back To Bed. This one alone worked for me. This method will at least make you dream more vividly if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t gift you lucid dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wild---wake-induced-lucid-dream&#34;&gt;WILD - Wake-Induced Lucid Dream&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next one, have you ever tried to make yourself think what you gonna dream tonight? You close your eyes and start thinking about a random scenario, a scenario where you living a life detached from the society full of creeps. Where you live in peace, do farming, build your house and many more shit. I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether am I the only person to think like that or not but you have to do it for to get A FREAKING LUCID DREAM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell yourself that you&amp;rsquo;ll lucid dream and keep visualizing things that you want to see.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sadly, this method alone won&amp;rsquo;t work, for me it didn&amp;rsquo;t. You have to combine other methods with that to make it work. This one was &lt;em&gt;WILD-Wake-Induced Lucid Dream&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fild---finger-induced-lucid-dream&#34;&gt;FILD - FInger-Induced Lucid Dream&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s more like pseudo movement of your limbs or fingers. You just trick your brain so that it thinks that you are moving or doing something while you&amp;rsquo;re still lying on bed. You may move your finger a bit but that should be so lightly that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t even look like it&amp;rsquo;s been moved. Consider playing an instrument or the best is typing with keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try combining this with &lt;em&gt;WILD&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-i-did-to-achieve-lucid-dream&#34;&gt;What I did to achieve Lucid Dream?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me it was quite simple. I combined all these methods and fell asleep on the usual time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I set an alarm for 3 hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I woke up and stayed for few minutes, I walked a bit, went washroom, and the again lying on the bed started thinking that I&amp;rsquo;ll lucid dream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The next thing I did was make myself think I am moving, doing things with my limbs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One thing, try to lie in bed with a different or unusual position. Maybe change or reverse the sleeping position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While my eyes were closed I tried to move my eyeballs like we do while we actually see things with opened eyes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Then I focused on hearing things around me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try best to rest your body and make yourself comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hopefully you&amp;rsquo;ll achieve what you wanted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So that&amp;rsquo;s what I did to get this weird thing working. It was an amazing feeling. The dream was a bit different, when I did it first I saw that I was in my house and could go anywhere and do anything. But I couldn&amp;rsquo;t visit a certain room as it was dark and it felt like there was a invisible barrier. However the dream felt a bit dark, light wasn&amp;rsquo;t that bright, the color of wall was not exactly how it was in real. I didn&amp;rsquo;t see anyone it was just me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second time I failed and it was kind of scary and also disappointing. I did everything but I actually got stuck and couldn&amp;rsquo;t move at all. I felt like a dark black colored human like thing cuddling with me. It sounds so nice as I nicely described but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t so satisfying, hahaha. So yes, it was sleep paralysis. I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered it several times in my life. Though that time it made so tired that when it got away I found myself sweating badly. I may have said something regarding this on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images&#34;&gt;image section of this site&lt;/a&gt; about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;look, how romantic it is!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/lucid-dream/sleep-paralysis.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;[Sleep-paralysis]&#34; title=&#34;Sleep paralysis&#34; style=&#34;width: 600px&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite failing and going through a sleep paralysis, I tried once again. Though it wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite like a lucid dream. Later I felt like It will be a waste of time for me so I then didn&amp;rsquo;t try it anymore as it badly affected my sleep cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-one-shouldnt-try-lucid-dreaming&#34;&gt;Why one shouldn&amp;rsquo;t try lucid dreaming?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, if you have got a lot of time for sleeping, don&amp;rsquo;t care about your mental health and want to explore your dreams more deeply then hell yeah, do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But if you got work and have to wake up early or you being a student, I&amp;rsquo;ll say it&amp;rsquo;s not worth it. It&amp;rsquo;s just a thing for people who have got a chance to sleep the next day away. Also it keeps bad impact on your health. Some people even fell way worse things than me. Just join this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/LucidDreaming&#34;&gt;subreddit&lt;/a&gt;, here they share many things about lucid dreaming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So that was all about LUCID DREAMING!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is love? Baby don&#39;t hurt me... - Haddaway</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/oh-my-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:33:44 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/oh-my-flower/</guid>
      <description>
    &lt;style&gt;
    .post-content img, .post-content a img {
        align-self: center;
        max-width: 100%; 
        width: 1000px; 
        height: auto; 
        padding: 0.5rem 1rem 0.5rem 1rem;
    }
    &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet another blog it is! I&amp;rsquo;ll write about something that none of you may have expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone in their life goes through it, and they sacrifice everything for it. They put a lot of efforts but does it actually help? Well, it depends. Some can make it and the rest move on. Move on with an intention to be better next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently read an article that actually opened my mind. I am going through pretty bad time of my life I&amp;rsquo;ll say. I am no good writer who can encourage or motivate you, but I&amp;rsquo;ve something that can actually help you go through it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;ll mark some lines from the article named &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://markmanson.net/love&#34;&gt;Love Is Not Enough&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; which is written by &lt;a href=&#34;https://markmanson.net/about&#34;&gt;Mark Manson&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how he came up with this, but everyone should read it even if they haven&amp;rsquo;t experienced the so-called love thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First he started with two characters. One idealized love and another didn&amp;rsquo;t. Idealizing love means taking love as a solution to all of his problems. Thus, we experience that dark side of &amp;ldquo;love&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
And because we idealize love, we overestimate it. As a result, our relationships pay a price.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the article I found something called &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://markmanson.net/personal-values&#34;&gt;fundamental values&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; of love I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But some hints were given such as respect, humility and commitment. We had a commitment which failed nicely. But we didn&amp;rsquo;t have those two things respect and humility. And yeah, we fought a lot. We blamed each other. Ruined day and nights. So messed up shit it was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toxic relationships are kind of like a boat on emotions. Keep rowing, and suddenly it gets overwhelmed with emotions and both sink in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
After all, if love solves everything, then why bother with all the other stuff? all the hard stuff?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Idealizing love causes unrealistic expectations about love. Let us dive in to three harsh truths about love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;love-does-not-equal-compatibility&#34;&gt;Love Does Not Equal Compatibility&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
Just because you fall in love with someone doesn&#39;t necessarily mean they?re a good partner for you to be with over the long term. Love is an &lt;b style=&#34;color:red;&#34;&gt;emotional&lt;/b&gt; process. Compatibility is a &lt;b style=&#34;color:red;&#34;&gt;logical&lt;/b&gt; process. And the two don&#39;t bleed into one another very well.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s true. Did anyone say that if you love someone that means they are the perfect one for you? The article also mentions that,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
It&#39;s possible to fall in love with somebody who sucks for us and our happiness.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
It&#39;s possible to fall in love with somebody who has different ambitions or life goals that are contradictory to our own, who holds different philosophical beliefs or worldviews that clash with our own sense of reality.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We feel the spark, and we jump and we fall. That&amp;rsquo;s how things work in a toxic relation. Then we consider that what went wrong? But what actually went wrong is,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
It went wrong before it even began.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not wrong to love someone, but we fail to understand the fundamental values of love that is mentioned in the article. We don&amp;rsquo;t value each other&amp;rsquo;s ambitions, thoughts and worldviews. We consider them to be like us. Thus forcing them to be one of us cause clashes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;love-does-not-solve-your-relationship-problems&#34;&gt;Love Does Not Solve Your Relationship Problems&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently found a comment on Reddit that said,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;If you&amp;rsquo;re ever walking in the woods, and you see the same tree twice, you&amp;rsquo;re lost son&amp;rdquo; was the best relationship advice my grandpa told me&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really liked it. That actually clarifies that if a relationship fails once it will hardly succeed. Obviously there are exceptions but let&amp;rsquo;s talk about majority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So talking in emotions make problems look like they are solvable but in reality it isn&amp;rsquo;t. Keep doing the same thing such as patching it again then getting hurt is just an absolute truth in those relationships that failed once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But who actually think logically on those times? Nobody.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we should learn is,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
While love may make you feel better about your relationship problems, it doesn&#39;t actually solve any of your relationship problems.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;love-is-not-always-worth-sacrificing-yourself-for&#34;&gt;Love Is Not Always Worth Sacrificing Yourself For&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obsession is a pretty bad thing. Obsession leads you to addiction. Addiction is way worse. When we love someone in a crazy sense it will eventually fail. Cause there will be questions in your mind that why I am not getting what I give, I don&amp;rsquo;t get the same love, I treat them well but do they? And many other questions will rise like these.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If respecting each other if one still gets this questions then yes maybe they are not the right person for you. I believe why wasting time like this? You give love, in return you get nothing. Then why still be there? Be there because of addiction or the hell called obsession. If you one wants to unfuck a relation then fuck the obsession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
In loving relationships, it&#39;s normal for both people to occasionally sacrifice their own desires, their own needs, and their own time for one another. I would argue that this is normal and healthy and a big part of what makes a relationship so great.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What love it is if you don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
But when it comes to sacrificing one&#39;s self-respect, one&#39;s dignity, one&#39;s physical body, one&#39;s ambitions and life purpose, just to be with someone, then that same love becomes problematic.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p style=&#34;color:rgb(226, 108, 216);  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
A loving relationship is supposed to supplement our individual identity, not damage it or replace it.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we still tolerate those damages that we both make just for the sake of love and affection, or I&amp;rsquo;ll say obsession. We fail to differentiate love and obsession. Whatever I shall make another post about obsession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if we keep holding it then we will allow ruining our self-respect and image. This way our energy will get sucked which we don&amp;rsquo;t want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now the part that actually I needed which is &lt;em&gt;The Friendship Test&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some parts from the article says,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
One of the oldest pieces of relationship advice in the book is, &lt;p style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;You and your partner should be best friends.?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt; Most people look at that piece of advice in the positive: I should spend time with my partner like I do with my best friend, I should communicate openly with my partner like I do with my best friend, I should have fun with my partner like I do with my best friend.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But people should also look at it in the negative:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color:rgb(226, 108, 216);  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
Would you tolerate your partner&#39;s negative behaviors in your best friend?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I answer then obviously not. With friends, I am not afraid of saying any bullshit. They ought to accept my dark humour, stupidity, fun and jokes whatsoever. I&amp;rsquo;ll be open to them. A friend is made with trust so love is. But if you can&amp;rsquo;t do the same with your partner then what freedom you get? At the end of the day you have to be with your friends just to share something that makes both of you laugh. Well, obviously we should be respectful then treat our loved ones a friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our partner should be our best friend but being in the boundary I believe. Being open and less judgemental is so important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
Why do we tolerate behavior in our romantic relationships that we would never ever, ever tolerate in our friendships?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy answer is that we are in love that&amp;rsquo;s why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Final thing to remember,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
The only way you can fully enjoy the love in your life is to choose to make something else more important in your life than love.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, love is a nice thing to experience. Loving someone isn&amp;rsquo;t bad. We can fall in love on those who might be bad for use even good for us. But we should not be sacrificing these few things such as self-respect, dignity, ability to trust because they are hard to get back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should let go. Not think that we won&amp;rsquo;t get someone like them in our life again. Be happy. Get indulged in sadness. Let us feel the pain. It is a lesson. Oh! I should mention something!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why don&amp;rsquo;t you read this masterpiece? A book called &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://nibmehub.com/opac-service/pdf/read/The%20Subtle%20Art%20of%20Not%20Giving%20a%20Fck%20A%20Counterintuitive%20Approach%20to%20Living%20a%20Good%20Life%20by%20Mark%20Manson%20(z-lib.org).pdf&#34;&gt;The Subtle Art of Not Giving a Fuck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; You can buy if you want. But a direct PDF link is attached here. I&amp;rsquo;ll highly suggest reading this book. It covers a lot of lessons that one must be aware of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me taking a nap helps a lot. Getting busy is the solution. Replacing never should be a solution cause now you seek attention, now you seek the cure of your loneliness not love. Write like me. Keep notes, it helps. We should not love those who don&amp;rsquo;t love us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time is the only cure.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img class=&#34;post-center-image&#34; src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/fire_writing.gif&#34; alt=&#34;[Fire writing]&#34; title=&#34;Fire writing&#34; style=&#34;width: 500px;&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally I should stop writing. If you have read all of these from the beginning I thank you very much. I write blog posts just to spend my time, and it feels better to express my thoughts. Who cares whether someone has read it or not. Self-satisfaction i&amp;rsquo;ll say. At least I can fill that &amp;ldquo;Posts&amp;rdquo; page with something. Post which is huge like this looks cool though.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something sweet</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/something-sweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:47:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/something-sweet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I ate something different. A different recipe I&amp;rsquo;ve found. Last time I cooked noodles and now I present you this! I actually don&amp;rsquo;t know what to name it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was starving and I didn&amp;rsquo;t even have the time to go out and bring something. I thought why not try something new with what I have within my reach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve eaten this kind of food before. That brown juice kind of thing is from date. The ingredients are actually,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bread slices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Date Juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powdered Milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Banana slices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just mixed these and I could add some more stuff if I had. I found these things near so I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother thinking of adding more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may try this if you are curious or like to try weird or different foods.
It tasted good. However I don&amp;rsquo;t really like sweets and foods that has sugar. But it was not bad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First meal of 2025</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/first_meal_2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 19:49:38 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/first_meal_2025/</guid>
      <description>
    &lt;style&gt;
    .post-content img, .post-content a img {
        align-self: center;
        max-width: 100%; 
        width: 1000px; 
        height: auto; 
        padding: 0.5rem 1rem 0.5rem 1rem;
    }
    &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just cooked my first meal of this year. So it&amp;rsquo;s a new year and Today I woke up early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just thought it&amp;rsquo;s better I try something new today. So why don&amp;rsquo;t I make my own breakfast?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Noodles was the only food I knew how to cook. So I started cooking. I took  noodles, then egg and some veggies (actually left over salad from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s party).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However it wasn&amp;rsquo;t cooked properly. But still it looked so good. But as I didn&amp;rsquo;t put salt or any other spices, it tasted&amp;hellip; okay. Not the best but one who starving will obviously eat.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img class=&#34;post-center-image&#34; src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/noodles.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;[Noodles Image]&#34; title=&#34;Nooooodles&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found it looking good. I wish I could make it more tasty. But I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make it any other day. Making my own breakfast was fun. But time consuming. It gives pleasure. We should try making our own food. Getting up early may also be another reason that made cooking breakfast so fun. The morning light and air is so so pure and refreshing. For me winter morning is the best!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>