<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>daily-things on 8amiul&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>https://8amiul.github.io/tags/daily-things/</link>
    <description>Recent content in daily-things on 8amiul&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:47:30 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://8amiul.github.io/tags/daily-things/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lucid Dream</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/lucid-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 04:47:30 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/lucid-dream/</guid>
      <description>
    &lt;style&gt;
    .post-content img, .post-content a img{
        align-self: center;
        max-width: 100%; 
        width: 1000px; 
        height: auto; 
        padding: 0.5rem 1rem 0.5rem 1rem;
    }
    &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dream is a fascinating phenomena. There are few types of dream. Some has an aspiration, that&amp;rsquo;s one kind of dream, some see they are being haunted by a huge human like entity who got no facial structure just like a mannequin, some see many other interesting things&amp;hellip; which is not our matter of discussion. However, Lucid dreaming is something which allows us to control what we see in our dreams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, It&amp;rsquo;s kind of like the scene from Mr. Robot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mind Awake, body asleep&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/lucid-dream/mr-robot.webp&#34; alt=&#34;[mr-robot]&#34; title=&#34;Mr. Robot&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, you&amp;rsquo;ll have the full access to do everything, have the allowance to choose and face consequences. But achieving a lucid dream isn&amp;rsquo;t a piece of cake. I was able to lucid dream after continuously trying for a week. You may fail at first attempt, but one can do anything if he has the will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I should share some tips which are followed by lucid dreamers in order to get this insane thing,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought why do we see dreams so vividly when it&amp;rsquo;s early in the morning? around 4-5 o&amp;rsquo;clock. That&amp;rsquo;s the best time for you to lucid dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now get ready to sacrifice your sleep and mental health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wbtb---wake-back-to-bed&#34;&gt;WBTB - Wake Back To Bed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set an alarm for 30 minutes or an hour after you fall asleep. Try to wake up multiple times like this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you&amp;rsquo;ll wake up try staying for at least 5 minutes. On those 5 minutes try to write down what you&amp;rsquo;ve seen, what you&amp;rsquo;ll see or just think that you have to lucid dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That was the first technique called WBTB-Wake Back To Bed. This one alone worked for me. This method will at least make you dream more vividly if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t gift you lucid dream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;wild---wake-induced-lucid-dream&#34;&gt;WILD - Wake-Induced Lucid Dream&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next one, have you ever tried to make yourself think what you gonna dream tonight? You close your eyes and start thinking about a random scenario, a scenario where you living a life detached from the society full of creeps. Where you live in peace, do farming, build your house and many more shit. I don&amp;rsquo;t know whether am I the only person to think like that or not but you have to do it for to get A FREAKING LUCID DREAM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell yourself that you&amp;rsquo;ll lucid dream and keep visualizing things that you want to see.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sadly, this method alone won&amp;rsquo;t work, for me it didn&amp;rsquo;t. You have to combine other methods with that to make it work. This one was &lt;em&gt;WILD-Wake-Induced Lucid Dream&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fild---finger-induced-lucid-dream&#34;&gt;FILD - FInger-Induced Lucid Dream&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s more like pseudo movement of your limbs or fingers. You just trick your brain so that it thinks that you are moving or doing something while you&amp;rsquo;re still lying on bed. You may move your finger a bit but that should be so lightly that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t even look like it&amp;rsquo;s been moved. Consider playing an instrument or the best is typing with keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try combining this with &lt;em&gt;WILD&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-i-did-to-achieve-lucid-dream&#34;&gt;What I did to achieve Lucid Dream?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me it was quite simple. I combined all these methods and fell asleep on the usual time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I set an alarm for 3 hours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I woke up and stayed for few minutes, I walked a bit, went washroom, and the again lying on the bed started thinking that I&amp;rsquo;ll lucid dream.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The next thing I did was make myself think I am moving, doing things with my limbs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One thing, try to lie in bed with a different or unusual position. Maybe change or reverse the sleeping position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While my eyes were closed I tried to move my eyeballs like we do while we actually see things with opened eyes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve to think in a first person view rather than a third person. Keep visualizing that it&amp;rsquo;s one kind of virtual reality headset you&amp;rsquo;re wearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Then I focused on hearing things around me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try best to rest your body and make yourself comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hopefully you&amp;rsquo;ll achieve what you wanted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So that&amp;rsquo;s what I did to get this weird thing working. It was an amazing feeling. The dream was a bit different, when I did it first I saw that I was in my house and could go anywhere and do anything. But I couldn&amp;rsquo;t visit a certain room as it was dark and it felt like there was a invisible barrier. However the dream felt a bit dark, light wasn&amp;rsquo;t that bright, the color of wall was not exactly how it was in real. I didn&amp;rsquo;t see anyone it was just me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second time I failed and it was kind of scary and also disappointing. I did everything but I actually got stuck and couldn&amp;rsquo;t move at all. I felt like a dark black colored human like thing cuddling with me. It sounds so nice as I nicely described but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t so satisfying, hahaha. So yes, it was sleep paralysis. I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered it several times in my life. Though that time it made so tired that when it got away I found myself sweating badly. I may have said something regarding this on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images&#34;&gt;image section of this site&lt;/a&gt; about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;look, how romantic it is!&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/posts/lucid-dream/sleep-paralysis.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;[Sleep-paralysis]&#34; title=&#34;Sleep paralysis&#34; style=&#34;width: 600px&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite failing and going through a sleep paralysis, I tried once again. Though it wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite like a lucid dream. Later I felt like It will be a waste of time for me so I then didn&amp;rsquo;t try it anymore as it badly affected my sleep cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-one-shouldnt-try-lucid-dreaming&#34;&gt;Why one shouldn&amp;rsquo;t try lucid dreaming?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, if you have got a lot of time for sleeping, don&amp;rsquo;t care about your mental health and want to explore your dreams more deeply then hell yeah, do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But if you got work and have to wake up early or you being a student, I&amp;rsquo;ll say it&amp;rsquo;s not worth it. It&amp;rsquo;s just a thing for people who have got a chance to sleep the next day away. Also it keeps bad impact on your health. Some people even fell way worse things than me. Just join this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/LucidDreaming&#34;&gt;subreddit&lt;/a&gt;, here they share many things about lucid dreaming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So that was all about LUCID DREAMING!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is love? Baby don&#39;t hurt me... - Haddaway</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/oh-my-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:33:44 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/oh-my-flower/</guid>
      <description>
    &lt;style&gt;
    .post-content img, .post-content a img {
        align-self: center;
        max-width: 100%; 
        width: 1000px; 
        height: auto; 
        padding: 0.5rem 1rem 0.5rem 1rem;
    }
    &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet another blog it is! I&amp;rsquo;ll write about something that none of you may have expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone in their life goes through it, and they sacrifice everything for it. They put a lot of efforts but does it actually help? Well, it depends. Some can make it and the rest move on. Move on with an intention to be better next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently read an article that actually opened my mind. I am going through pretty bad time of my life I&amp;rsquo;ll say. I am no good writer who can encourage or motivate you, but I&amp;rsquo;ve something that can actually help you go through it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;ll mark some lines from the article named &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://markmanson.net/love&#34;&gt;Love Is Not Enough&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; which is written by &lt;a href=&#34;https://markmanson.net/about&#34;&gt;Mark Manson&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know how he came up with this, but everyone should read it even if they haven&amp;rsquo;t experienced the so-called love thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First he started with two characters. One idealized love and another didn&amp;rsquo;t. Idealizing love means taking love as a solution to all of his problems. Thus, we experience that dark side of &amp;ldquo;love&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
And because we idealize love, we overestimate it. As a result, our relationships pay a price.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the article I found something called &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://markmanson.net/personal-values&#34;&gt;fundamental values&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; of love I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But some hints were given such as respect, humility and commitment. We had a commitment which failed nicely. But we didn&amp;rsquo;t have those two things respect and humility. And yeah, we fought a lot. We blamed each other. Ruined day and nights. So messed up shit it was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Toxic relationships are kind of like a boat on emotions. Keep rowing, and suddenly it gets overwhelmed with emotions and both sink in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
After all, if love solves everything, then why bother with all the other stuff? all the hard stuff?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Idealizing love causes unrealistic expectations about love. Let us dive in to three harsh truths about love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;love-does-not-equal-compatibility&#34;&gt;Love Does Not Equal Compatibility&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
Just because you fall in love with someone doesn&#39;t necessarily mean they?re a good partner for you to be with over the long term. Love is an &lt;b style=&#34;color:red;&#34;&gt;emotional&lt;/b&gt; process. Compatibility is a &lt;b style=&#34;color:red;&#34;&gt;logical&lt;/b&gt; process. And the two don&#39;t bleed into one another very well.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s true. Did anyone say that if you love someone that means they are the perfect one for you? The article also mentions that,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
It&#39;s possible to fall in love with somebody who sucks for us and our happiness.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
It&#39;s possible to fall in love with somebody who has different ambitions or life goals that are contradictory to our own, who holds different philosophical beliefs or worldviews that clash with our own sense of reality.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We feel the spark, and we jump and we fall. That&amp;rsquo;s how things work in a toxic relation. Then we consider that what went wrong? But what actually went wrong is,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
It went wrong before it even began.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not wrong to love someone, but we fail to understand the fundamental values of love that is mentioned in the article. We don&amp;rsquo;t value each other&amp;rsquo;s ambitions, thoughts and worldviews. We consider them to be like us. Thus forcing them to be one of us cause clashes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;love-does-not-solve-your-relationship-problems&#34;&gt;Love Does Not Solve Your Relationship Problems&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently found a comment on Reddit that said,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;If you&amp;rsquo;re ever walking in the woods, and you see the same tree twice, you&amp;rsquo;re lost son&amp;rdquo; was the best relationship advice my grandpa told me&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really liked it. That actually clarifies that if a relationship fails once it will hardly succeed. Obviously there are exceptions but let&amp;rsquo;s talk about majority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So talking in emotions make problems look like they are solvable but in reality it isn&amp;rsquo;t. Keep doing the same thing such as patching it again then getting hurt is just an absolute truth in those relationships that failed once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But who actually think logically on those times? Nobody.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What we should learn is,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
While love may make you feel better about your relationship problems, it doesn&#39;t actually solve any of your relationship problems.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;love-is-not-always-worth-sacrificing-yourself-for&#34;&gt;Love Is Not Always Worth Sacrificing Yourself For&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obsession is a pretty bad thing. Obsession leads you to addiction. Addiction is way worse. When we love someone in a crazy sense it will eventually fail. Cause there will be questions in your mind that why I am not getting what I give, I don&amp;rsquo;t get the same love, I treat them well but do they? And many other questions will rise like these.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If respecting each other if one still gets this questions then yes maybe they are not the right person for you. I believe why wasting time like this? You give love, in return you get nothing. Then why still be there? Be there because of addiction or the hell called obsession. If you one wants to unfuck a relation then fuck the obsession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
In loving relationships, it&#39;s normal for both people to occasionally sacrifice their own desires, their own needs, and their own time for one another. I would argue that this is normal and healthy and a big part of what makes a relationship so great.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What love it is if you don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
But when it comes to sacrificing one&#39;s self-respect, one&#39;s dignity, one&#39;s physical body, one&#39;s ambitions and life purpose, just to be with someone, then that same love becomes problematic.
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p style=&#34;color:rgb(226, 108, 216);  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
A loving relationship is supposed to supplement our individual identity, not damage it or replace it.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we still tolerate those damages that we both make just for the sake of love and affection, or I&amp;rsquo;ll say obsession. We fail to differentiate love and obsession. Whatever I shall make another post about obsession.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So if we keep holding it then we will allow ruining our self-respect and image. This way our energy will get sucked which we don&amp;rsquo;t want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now the part that actually I needed which is &lt;em&gt;The Friendship Test&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some parts from the article says,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
One of the oldest pieces of relationship advice in the book is, &lt;p style=&#34;color: gray;&#34;&gt;You and your partner should be best friends.?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt; Most people look at that piece of advice in the positive: I should spend time with my partner like I do with my best friend, I should communicate openly with my partner like I do with my best friend, I should have fun with my partner like I do with my best friend.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But people should also look at it in the negative:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color:rgb(226, 108, 216);  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
Would you tolerate your partner&#39;s negative behaviors in your best friend?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I answer then obviously not. With friends, I am not afraid of saying any bullshit. They ought to accept my dark humour, stupidity, fun and jokes whatsoever. I&amp;rsquo;ll be open to them. A friend is made with trust so love is. But if you can&amp;rsquo;t do the same with your partner then what freedom you get? At the end of the day you have to be with your friends just to share something that makes both of you laugh. Well, obviously we should be respectful then treat our loved ones a friend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our partner should be our best friend but being in the boundary I believe. Being open and less judgemental is so important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
Why do we tolerate behavior in our romantic relationships that we would never ever, ever tolerate in our friendships?
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Easy answer is that we are in love that&amp;rsquo;s why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Final thing to remember,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#34;color: #B9B28A;  font-style: italic;&#34;&gt;
The only way you can fully enjoy the love in your life is to choose to make something else more important in your life than love.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yeah, love is a nice thing to experience. Loving someone isn&amp;rsquo;t bad. We can fall in love on those who might be bad for use even good for us. But we should not be sacrificing these few things such as self-respect, dignity, ability to trust because they are hard to get back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You should let go. Not think that we won&amp;rsquo;t get someone like them in our life again. Be happy. Get indulged in sadness. Let us feel the pain. It is a lesson. Oh! I should mention something!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why don&amp;rsquo;t you read this masterpiece? A book called &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://nibmehub.com/opac-service/pdf/read/The%20Subtle%20Art%20of%20Not%20Giving%20a%20Fck%20A%20Counterintuitive%20Approach%20to%20Living%20a%20Good%20Life%20by%20Mark%20Manson%20(z-lib.org).pdf&#34;&gt;The Subtle Art of Not Giving a Fuck&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; You can buy if you want. But a direct PDF link is attached here. I&amp;rsquo;ll highly suggest reading this book. It covers a lot of lessons that one must be aware of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me taking a nap helps a lot. Getting busy is the solution. Replacing never should be a solution cause now you seek attention, now you seek the cure of your loneliness not love. Write like me. Keep notes, it helps. We should not love those who don&amp;rsquo;t love us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Time is the only cure.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img class=&#34;post-center-image&#34; src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/fire_writing.gif&#34; alt=&#34;[Fire writing]&#34; title=&#34;Fire writing&#34; style=&#34;width: 500px;&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally I should stop writing. If you have read all of these from the beginning I thank you very much. I write blog posts just to spend my time, and it feels better to express my thoughts. Who cares whether someone has read it or not. Self-satisfaction i&amp;rsquo;ll say. At least I can fill that &amp;ldquo;Posts&amp;rdquo; page with something. Post which is huge like this looks cool though.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something sweet</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/something-sweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 22:47:21 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/something-sweet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I ate something different. A different recipe I&amp;rsquo;ve found. Last time I cooked noodles and now I present you this! I actually don&amp;rsquo;t know what to name it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was starving and I didn&amp;rsquo;t even have the time to go out and bring something. I thought why not try something new with what I have within my reach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve eaten this kind of food before. That brown juice kind of thing is from date. The ingredients are actually,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bread slices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Date Juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Powdered Milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Banana slices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just mixed these and I could add some more stuff if I had. I found these things near so I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother thinking of adding more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may try this if you are curious or like to try weird or different foods.
It tasted good. However I don&amp;rsquo;t really like sweets and foods that has sugar. But it was not bad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First meal of 2025</title>
      <link>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/first_meal_2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 19:49:38 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://8amiul.github.io/posts/first_meal_2025/</guid>
      <description>
    &lt;style&gt;
    .post-content img, .post-content a img {
        align-self: center;
        max-width: 100%; 
        width: 1000px; 
        height: auto; 
        padding: 0.5rem 1rem 0.5rem 1rem;
    }
    &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just cooked my first meal of this year. So it&amp;rsquo;s a new year and Today I woke up early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just thought it&amp;rsquo;s better I try something new today. So why don&amp;rsquo;t I make my own breakfast?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Noodles was the only food I knew how to cook. So I started cooking. I took  noodles, then egg and some veggies (actually left over salad from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s party).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However it wasn&amp;rsquo;t cooked properly. But still it looked so good. But as I didn&amp;rsquo;t put salt or any other spices, it tasted&amp;hellip; okay. Not the best but one who starving will obviously eat.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;img class=&#34;post-center-image&#34; src=&#34;https://8amiul.github.io/images/noodles.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;[Noodles Image]&#34; title=&#34;Nooooodles&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found it looking good. I wish I could make it more tasty. But I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make it any other day. Making my own breakfast was fun. But time consuming. It gives pleasure. We should try making our own food. Getting up early may also be another reason that made cooking breakfast so fun. The morning light and air is so so pure and refreshing. For me winter morning is the best!&lt;/p&gt;
</description> 
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>